Guide to the African American Chamber of Commerce of Western Pennsylvania Digital Archive AACCWP
ULS Archives & Special Collections
- Communications, I.
  - Newspaper & Magazine Articles/Media Clippings, 3.
    - Fab 40 Honorees - Shawn Hicks - NPC, 2012
    - African American Chamber Breakfast - Nova Touts Marcellus Benefits - NPC, January 2012
    - A Model for Creating an Even Better Pittsburgh Region for all - Imagine Pittsburgh Now, January 2012
    - Lamb Talks Fiscal Health at PowerBreakfast - NPC, February 2012
    - Pittsburgh Women History Makers - NPC, February 2012
    - AAChamber Sponsors Diabetes Seminar - NPC, March 2012
    - Fitzgerald-College Grads Have ReplacedSteel in Refueling Pittsburgh's Growth - NPC, March 2012
    - West Penn Hospital CEO at Chamber Breakfast - NPC, April 2012
    - Chamber Charts New Course - NPC, May 2012
    - City's Equal Opportunity Report Raises Questions-NPC, June 2012
    - Wagner at Chamber Breakfast - NPC, July 2012
    - Casey Q&A at PowerBreakfast - NPC, August 2012
    - Fed Reserve VP Ralks Recovery - PC, October 2012
    - 50 Men of Excellence Reception - NPC, November 2012
    - Yablonsky Keynotes Chamber Lunch, Cites Diversity as a Regional Challenge - PC, December 2012
    - Strengthening Business Acumen in Western Pennsylvania - Urban Connection, January 2013
    - Williams Gives Chamber Alcosan Project Update - PC, January 2012
    - Making Shale Inclusive - PC, February 2012
    - Pittsburgh Inclusion News - Vibrant Pittsburgh, February 2013
    - Fitzgerald Talks Transit and Jobs at Chamber Breakfast - PC, April 2013
    - Few Surprises at Chamber Forum - PC, May 2012
    - Highmark Chief Keynotes Chamber Business Luncheon - PC, May 2013
    - Doris Carson Williams Earns Certified Chamber Executive Certification - NPC, August 2013
    - Teshome Gives Business Forecast to Chamber - NPC, October 2013
    - African American Chamber Luncheon Highlights Connecting with Partners, December 2013
    - Rich Fitzgerald Talks about growth at AACCWP, January 2014
    - Mayor Peduto Focus on Small Neighborhood Development, March 2014
    - Chamber and Conference make for engaging PowerBreakfast, May 2014
    - Federal Reserve Bank VP makes economic forecast at AACCWP PowerBreakfast, June 2014
    - UPMC Rob DeMichiei pushes diversity at African American Chamber Breakfast, September 2014
    - CCAC President Bullock welcomed at Chamber PowerBreakfast, October 2014
    - African American Chamber hosts Annual Luncheon with David Porges of EQT, December 2014
    - Fitzgerald touts partnerships at Chamber Breakfast, January 2015
    - Ellen McLean talks PAT capital projects at PowerBreakfast Meeting, February 2015
    - Mayor Peduto talks culture change at PowerBreakfast, March 2015
    - Keith Key talks development and inclusion at Chamber PowerBreakfast, April 2015
    - Mayor Peduto and Highmark CEO highlight African American Chamber Luncheon, May 2015
    - Carnegie Museums update given to African American Chamber Members, June 2015
    - Pittsburgh Police Chief strives to hire more minority officers, July 2015
    - Programs geared to help small business prosper, August 2015
    - Pirates Coonelly pushes for greater urban focus for baseball, September 2015
    - Waldrup promotes Downtown Partnership at PowerBreakfast, October 2015
    - Cassotis makes three point landing at PowerBreakfast, November 2015
    - Beacon system improves city's small and minority business contracting outreach, December 2015
    - Governor Wolf praises African American Chamber in luncheon remarks, December 2015
    - State may have budget deal soon, December 2015
    - Fitzgerald addresses year's first PowerBreakfast, January 2016
    - Williams appointed head of Local Federal Reserve Board, January 2016
    - Davin Promotes inclusive development at Chamber Breakfast, February 2016
    - Mayor Peduto pushes access at PowerBreakfast, March 2016
    - Chamber Candidates Forum Yields enthusiasm and few surprises, April 2016
    - Yealy pushes building diversity on multiple levels at PowerBreakfast, April 2016
    - Smith pushes partnership and building economy at Chamber Breakfast, July 2016
    - Nicholson promotes The Frick at PowerBreakfast, September 2016
    - Pittsburgh Opera Director Hahn promotes Josh Gibson Story, October 2016
    - Federal Reserve Bank of Cleveland president gives economic forecast at Chamber luncheon, December 2016
    - Fitzgerald kicks off 2017 PowerBreakfast series, January 2017
  - Press Releases, 4.
    The Chamber issues press releases for all annual meetings, business luncheons, special events, and workshops. The purpose is to have a written or recorded communication that documents the organization's activities. Typically, they are sent electronically to assignment editors, station managers, and journalists.
    - Redevelopment Assistance Capital Program, February 1999
    - Councilman Sala Udin, March 8, 1999
    - Plan B Advocacy Meeting, March 2001
    - DOE and NETL Partnership, November 9, 2001
    - Concerns Over Living Wage Bill, December 3, 2001
    - 3rd Annual Business Luncheon, December 5, 2001
    - Candidates' Forum, April 10, 2002
    - Candidates' Forum, April 29, 2003
    - Fourth Annual Luncheon, May 20, 2003
    - Candidates' Forum, September 11, 2003
    - Public Hearing, October 9, 2003
    - FTAA Between FLT Trading, Inc and Equitable Gas Company, October 21, 2003
    - Fifth Annual Business Luncheon, December 3, 2003
    - PowerBreakfast Meeting, January 16, 2004
    - Annual Meeting Luncheon, May 10, 2004
    - Ask the Expert Program, September 2, 2004
    - PowerBreakfast Meeting, November 19, 2004
    - Annual Business Luncheon, December 1, 2004
    - PowerBreakfast, February 18, 2005
    - Candidates' Forum, April 21, 2005
    - Southwest Airlines President, May 12, 2005
    - Kwame Jackson, May 19, 2005
    - CCAC President, November 9, 2005
    - Equitable Resources Chairman, President, and CEO, November 9, 2005
    - Thomas Usher Entrepeneurial Spirit Program, May 2006
    - Chairman & CEO of U.S. Steel Corporation, May 12, 2006
    - PowerBreakfast Meeting, September 15, 2006
    - Robert Morris University President, October 20, 2006
    - Pittsburgh School Superintendant, January 10, 2007
    - Honorable Dennis Yablonsky, February 9, 2007
    - Mayor Ravenstahl, April 2, 2007
    - Duquesne Light President and CEO, April 23, 2007
    - Glen T. Meakem, May 30, 2007
    - U.S. Commissioner of the EEOC, June 11, 2007
    - New President & CPO of the United Way of Allegheny County, July 16, 2007
    - Chief Financial Officer of UPMC, September 19, 2007
    - Senior Vice President & Chief Economist of PNC FSG, October 10, 2007
    - President and CEO of UPMC, December 6, 2007
    - President and CEO of the August Wilson Center, February 7, 2008
    - President and CEO of Bayer Material Science, LLC, March 3, 2008
    - CEO of Landmarks Community Capital Corooration of Pittsburgh, April 11, 2008
    - University of Pittsburgh Vice Chancellor of Public Affairs, May 2, 2008
    - Stephen Bland, June 12, 2008
    - President and CEO of KBK Enterprises, July 11, 2008
    - AACC Tenth Anniversary, October 16, 2008
    - Chairman and CEO of WESCO Distribution, Inc, November 26, 2008
    - Allegheny County Chief Executive, January 9, 2009
    - Obama's Stimulus Package, April 17, 2009
    - Candidates Forum, April 23, 2009
    - President and CEO of Highmark, May 12, 2009
    - FRB of Cleveland Executive Vice President, September 9, 2009
    - Washington County Commissioner, October 12, 2009
    - BNY Mellon CEO, November 9, 2009
    - AACC Seasonal Celebration, October 17, 2009
    - Candidates' Forum, April 5, 2010
    - URA Executive Director, April 12, 2010
    - Pitt Chancellor and CEO, May 2, 2010
    - FedEx Ground Managing Director, September 15, 2010
    - iGate Corporation Co-Founder, October 1, 2010
    - Bayer CEO, November 16, 2010
    - LANXESS Corporation CEO, January 10, 2011
    - Marcellus Shale Coalition President and Executive Director, February 4, 2011
    - Pittsburgh Public School Superintendent, March 14, 2011
    - Allegheny County Executive and County Controller Candidates' Forum, April 27, 2011
    - CMU President, April 27, 2011
    - Diabetes Workshops, May 27, 2011
    - Jewish Healthcare Foundation, May 27, 2011
    - Port Authority Transit CEO, June 3, 2011
    - State Senator Wayne D. Fontana, July 8, 2011
    - UPMC Family Medicine Chair, August 22, 2011
    - Pittsburgh Police Chief, October 21, 2011
    - WQED, November 3, 2011
    - Carnegie Museums' President, November 8, 2011
    - NOVA Chemicals CEO, January 11, 2012
    - Dr. Jerome R. Gloster, February 13, 2012
    - Michael E. Lamb, February 13, 2012
    - Allegheny County Chief Executive, March 12, 2012
    - 24th Legislative District Candidates, March 28, 2013
    - Dollar Bank CEO, April 30, 2012
    - Dollar Bank CEO, May 4, 2012
    - Sixth Diabetes Workshop, May 9, 2012
    - Pennsylvania Auditor General, June 6, 2012
    - PAT CEO, June 6, 2012
    - Senator Bob Casey, August 1, 2012
    - Seventh Diabetes Workshop, September 10, 2012
    - Warhol Museum's Eric Shiner, September 10, 2012
    - Diabetes Workshop Grand Finale, November 5, 2012
    - Allegheny Conference on Community Development CEO, November 26, 2012
    - ALCOSAN Executive Director, January 7, 2013
    - Keith B. Key, April 5, 2013
    - Allegheny County Chief Executive, April 12, 2013
    - Mayoral Candidates' Forum, April 12, 2013
    - Highmark President and CEO, April 15, 2013
    - Daniel D. Fitzpatrick, July 15, 2013
    - Doris Carson Williams Earns Certified Chamber Executive Certification, August 19, 2013
    - Green Building Alliance CEO, September 16, 2013
    - County Executive Rich Fitzgerald of Allegheny County, January 15, 2016
    - Dennis Davin Secretary for the PA Department of Community and Economic Development, February 19, 2016
    - Pa House of Representatives, April 7, 2016
    - Patrick Gallagher Chancellor for the University of Pittsburgh, May 3, 2016
    - Lorretta Mester President and CEO of Federal Reserve Bank of Cleveland, November 30, 2016
- Events, II.
  The Chamber hosts an average of 35 scheduled activities each year, designed to engage and add value to the membership while increasing awareness about the organization to the general public.
  - Annual Business Luncheons, 1.
    Every December, the Chamber invites the Chairman or President of a major corporation to speak on what the region needs to do collectively to move from good to great. An average of 350–400 people from business, government, and state and local elected officials attend this annual event.
  - Annual Meeting & Luncheon, 2.
    There is a formal certification process Members submit to in order to attend the Annual Meetings. In recent years, the luncheon speaker meets privately with the members and answers their questions. The members then join the speaker to welcome the business representatives and guests for the luncheon.
    - Ralph Dickerson of United Way of New York City, May 19, 2000
    - Murry S. Gerber of Equitable Resources, Inc., May 15, 2001
    - Charles E. Bunch of PPG Industries, May 17, 2002
    - Ulice Payne, Jr. of Milwaukee Brewers Baseball Club, May 20, 2003
    - Senator Arlen Specter of United States Senate, May 10, 2004
    - Kwame Jackson of Kwame, Inc. and The Apprentice Show, May 19, 2005
    - John P. Surma, Jr. of United States Steel Corporation, May 12, 2006
    - Glen T. Meakem of Meakem Becker Venture Capital, May 30, 2007
    - Robert Hill of the University of Pittsburgh, May 14, 2008
    - Kenneth R. Melanie of Highmark Blue Cross Blue Shield, May 12, 2009
    - Mark Nordenberg of University of Pittsburgh, May 19, 2010
    - Jared L. Cohon of Carnegie Mellon University, May 13, 2011
    - Robert P. Oeler of Dollar Bank, May 10, 2012
    - William Winkenwerder Jr of Highmark Inc., May 1, 2013
    - William Demchak of PNC Financial Services Group, Inc., May 6, 2014
    - David Holmberg of Highmark, Inc., May 7, 2015
    - Patrick Gallagher of University of Pittsburgh, May 3, 2016
    - Michael McGarry of PPG Industries, May 9, 2017
  - Business Institute Workshops, 3.
    Each month the Chamber engages an expert in the field of legal, finance and accounting, information technology, or marketing and communications to provide training, coaching, and strengthening of a firm's business acumen to help them compete in the global marketplace. An average of 16 programs are held each year.
    - Ask the Expert Credit Restoration-Flyer, January 30, 2007
    - Ice Skating Party-Flyer, February 24, 2007
    - Business Risk Management Workshop-Flyer, March 27, 2007
    - How to do Business with CCAC-Flyer, April 5, 2007
    - Candidates' Forum-Flyer, April 11, 2007
    - Eighth Annual Meeting-Flyer, May 30, 2007
    - How to do Business with Duquesne Light-Flyer, June 14, 2007
    - Basics of Brand Development-Flyer, June 21, 2007
    - Technologically Speaking, You Are Your Brand-Flyer, August 28, 2007
    - Doing Business through the Pennsylvania Gaming Control Board-Flyer, September 20, 2007
    - How to do Business with the Housing Authority of the City of Pittsburgh-Flyer, October 30, 2007
    - Kick-Off the Holiday Season-Flyer, November 28, 2007
    - Business Luncheon Meeting-Flyer, December 6, 2007
    - Focus GroupTransportation Workshop-Flyer, February 20, 2008
    - Ice Skating Party-Flyer, February 23, 2008
    - How to do Business with the Forbes Funds-Flyer, February 26, 2008
    - Business and Access to Capital Workshop-Flyer, March 20, 2008
    - Ninth Annual Luncheon-Flyer, May 14, 2008
    - New Members' Orientation-Flyer, June 24, 2008
    - Consolidating City of Pittsburgh & Allegheny County Governments-Flyer, July 15, 2008
    - How to Understand Taxes, Grants, and Loans-Flyer, August 20, 2008
    - Tenth Anniversary-Flyer, October 28, 2008
    - Business Luncheon Meeting-Flyer, December 5, 2008
    - New Members' Orientation-Flyer, January 23, 2009
    - New Year's Celebration-Flyer, January 29, 2009
    - Ice Skating Party-Flyer, February 28, 2009
    - External Commercial Green Building-Flyer, March 9, 2009
    - Protecting Your Investments in Turbulent Times-Flyer, March 17, 2009
    - The Future of Green Jobs-Flyer, March 30, 2009
    - Candidates' Forum-Flyer, April 23, 2009
    - How IT Relates to Your Business-Flyer, April 29, 2009
    - Tenth Annual Meeting Luncheon-Flyer, May 12, 2009
    - Becoming LEED Certified-Flyer, June 8, 2009
    - Eliminating Racial and Ethnic Disparities in Health-Flyer, June 11, 2009
    - New Members' Orientation-Flyer, June 23, 2009
    - Transit Development Plan Workshop-Flyer, July 13, 2009
    - Highmark Update on Healthcare-Flyer, July 21, 2009
    - How to do Business with Point Park University-Flyer, August 18, 2009
    - Sustainability and Green Products-Flyer, September 28, 2009
    - Geting the Estimate Right-Flyer, October 14, 2009
    - How to do Business with Rivers Casino-Flyer, October 21, 2009
    - New Electricity and Natural Gas Pools-Flyer, November 10, 2009
    - Special Meeting-Mark S. Sniderman-Flyer, November 13, 2009
    - Seasonal Celebration-Flyer, November 30, 2009
    - Annual Business Luncheon-Flyer, December 2, 2009
    - LEED the way to Green Buildings-Flyer, December 8, 2009
    - Structureing the Sales Call-Flyer, February 3, 2010
    - New Members' Orientation-Flyer, February 5, 2010
    - Sickle Cell Disease-Flyer, February 11, 2010
    - Ice Skating Party-Flyer, February 27, 2010
    - Discussion on Legal Issues-Flyer, April 20, 2010
    - Candidates' Forum-Flyer, April 29, 2010
    - Annual Meeting and Luncheon-Flyer, May 19, 2010
    - Special Meeting CCAC Turner-Flyer, June 11, 2010
    - Social Media Workshop-Flyer, June 16, 2010
    - Members' Orientation-Flyer, July 8, 2010
    - How to do Business with Allegheny County Economic Development-Flyer, July 14, 2010
    - Diabetes Series-Flyer, October 2010
    - Legislative Reception and Briefing-Flyer, October 7, 2010
    - Time Management Workshop-Flyer, November 15, 2010
    - Seasonal Celebration-Flyer, November 29, 2010
    - Annual Business Luncheon-Flyer, December 2, 2010
    - Discussion on Legal Issues-Flyer, December 15, 2010
    - Members' Orientation-Flyer, February 4, 2011
    - SCORE-Flyer, February 10, 2011
    - Developing a Winning Business Plan-Flyer, February 22, 2011
    - Ice Skating Party-Flyer, February 26, 2011
    - Diabetes Self Management of a Chronic Disease-Flyer, March 10, 2011
    - How to do Business with CCAC-Flyer, March 11, 2011
    - Small Business Tax Workshop-Flyer, March 15, 2011
    - A Social Media Workshop-Flyer, April 12, 2011
    - Candidates' Forum-Flyer, May 9, 2011
    - An Interactive Social Media Workshop-Flyer, June 14, 2011
    - Community Partners Concert Boyz II Men-Flyer, June 23, 2011
    - Diabetes The Silent Killer-Flyer, June 29, 2011
    - How to do Business with Rivers Casino-Flyer, August 23, 2011
    - Diabetes The Silent Killer-Flyer, September 8, 2011
    - Communications Workshop-Flyer, September 13, 2011
    - Diabetes The Silent Killer-Flyer, November 17, 2011
    - Seasonal Celebration-Flyer, November 21, 2011
    - Annual Business Luncheon-Flyer, December 2, 2011
    - Members' Orientation-Flyer, January 25, 2012
    - Diabetes The Silent Killer Fitness and Eye Care-Flyer, February 21, 2012
    - Ice Skating Party-Flyer, February 25, 2012
    - Special Small Business Tax Workshop-Evaluation Summary, March 13, 2012
    - Special Small Business Tax Workshop-Flyer, March 13, 2012
    - Candidates' Forum-Flyer, April 12, 2012
    - How To Do Business With Allegheny County-Evaluation Results, April 17, 2012
    - How To Do Business With Allegheny County-Flyer, April 17, 2012
    - Diabetes The Silent Killer Proper Foot Care-Flyer, May 21, 2012
    - Members' Orientation-Flyer, June 26, 2012
    - Digging Out-Cleaning Up-Moving Forward-Flyer, July 12, 2012
    - Diabetes The Silent Killer-Flyer, September 26, 2012
    - How To Do Business In The Marcellus Shale-Flyer, October 10, 2012
    - Diabetes The Silent Killer Grand Finale-Flyer, November 13, 2012
    - Members' Seasonal Celebration-Flyer2, November 29, 2012
    - Annual Business Luncheon-Flyer, December 3, 2012
    - Open House-Flyer, January 22, 2013
    - Soul Food Junkies-Flyer, January 23, 2013
    - Power to Prosper Program-Evaluation Results, January 30, 2013
    - Power to Prosper Program-Flyer, January 30, 2013
    - The Marcellus Shale-Evaluation Results, January 31, 2013
    - The Marcellus Shale-Flyer, January 31, 2013
    - Members' Orientation-Flyer, February 19, 2013
    - How to do Business with the Housing Authority of the City of Pittsburgh-Flyer, March 12, 2013
    - The ABC's of Selling Online-Evaluation Summary, March 26, 2013
    - The ABC's of Selling Online-Flyer, March 26, 2013
    - Financial Planning Workshop-Evaluation Summary, April 4, 2013
    - Financial Planning Workshop-Flyer, April 4, 2013
    - Focus on Business Finances-Evaluation Summary, April 23, 2013
    - Focus on Business Finances-Flyer, April 23, 2013
    - Annual Meeting & Luncheon-Flyer, May 1, 2013
    - Candidates' Forum-Flyer, May 2, 2013
    - Members' Orientation-Flyer, June 19, 2013
    - Affordable Care Act Workshop-Evaluation Summary, September 12, 2013
    - Affordable Care Act Workshop-Flyer, September 12, 2013
    - How to do Business with the Highmark-Evaluation Summary, October 8, 2013
    - How to do Business with the Highmark-Flyer, October 8, 2013
    - Social Media Workshop-Evaluation Summary, October 30, 2013
    - Social Media Workshop-Flyer, October 30, 2013
    - Speed Networking-Evaluation Summary, November 20, 2013
    - Speed Networking-Flyer, November 20, 2013
    - Strategic Planning Workshop-Evaluation Summary, January 21, 2014
    - Strategic Planning Workshop-Flyer, January 21, 2014
    - Members' Orientation-Evaluation Summary, January 28, 2014
    - Members' Orientation-Flyer, January 28, 2014
    - How to do Business with Coca-Cola-Evaluation Summary, February 11, 2014
    - How to do Business with Coca-Cola-Flyer, February 11, 2014
    - Social Media Workshop-Evaluation Summary, Macrh 12, 2014
    - Social Media Workshop-Flyer, March 12, 2014
    - Private Equity Workshop-Evaluation Summary, March 18, 2014
    - Private Equity Workshop-Flyer, March 18, 2014
    - Structuring the Sales Call-Evaluation Summary, April 15, 2014
    - Structuring the Sales Call-Flyer, April 15, 2014
    - Update on the Affordable Care Act-Evaluation Summary
    - Update on the Affordable Care Act-Flyer, May 14, 2014
    - Members' Orientation-Evaluation Summary, June 30, 2014
    - Members' Orientation-Flyer, June 30, 2014
    - Opportunities of Small Business in the Marcellus Shale-Evaluation Summary, September 10, 2014
    - Opportunities of Small Business in the Marcellus Shale-Flyer, September 10, 2014
    - Accelerating Business Decisions-Evaluation Summary, September 27, 2014
    - Executing Strategy at the Front Line-Flyer, September 27, 2014
    - Discussion on Legal Issues-Evaluation Summary, October 15, 2014
    - Discussion on Legal Issues-Flyer, October 15, 2014
    - How To Do What You Do Sucessfully-Flyer, October 21, 2014
    - How To Do What You Do Sucessfully-Evaluation Summary, October 21, 2014
    - Structuring a Sales Call, March 11, 2015
    - Financial Statement Analysis and Budgeting, April 22, 2015
    - Crucial Business Trends for 2015, June 17, 2015
    - How to do Business with Allegheny County Airport Authority, July 22, 2015
    - The Impact of Ozone Regulations on Jobs in our Community, September 2, 2015
    - Cybersecurity Protecting Your Business, October 7, 2015
    - How to do Business with Carnegie Museums of Pittsburgh, November 16, 2015
    - Financial Health Workshop, January 20, 2016
    - Access to Capital Workshop, February 23, 2016
    - Supply Chain Program, February 25, 2016
    - Understanding Your Credit Report and Credit Score Workshop, March 30, 2016
    - How to do Business with Allegheny Health Network, April 12, 2016
    - Talent Issues and Options Workshop, May 18, 2016
    - Social Media Workshop, May 26, 2016
    - How to do Business with Urban Redevelopment Authority of Pittbsurgh, June 14, 2016
    - How to do Business with Highmark Health, September 20, 2016
    - Changes to Payroll Regulations Workshop, September 23, 2016
    - How to do Business with Allegheny County Airport Authority, October 5, 2016
    - Youth Development Workshop, October 19, 2016
    - Strategic Planning Workshop, January 12, 2017
    - Top Consumer Trends for 2017, February 15, 2017
    - How to do Business with Port Authority of Allegheny County, February 28, 2017
    - Winning Sales Techniques, March 21, 2017
    - Workforce and the American Job Center Workshop, April 27, 2017
    - Financial Workshop with Maher Duessel, May 11, 2017
    - How to do Business with ALCOSAN, June 7, 2017
    - Accessing Capital Workshop, June 14, 2017
    - Using the Media Effectively, September 14, 2017
    - Cybersecurity Workshop, October 19, 2017
    - Digital Marketing Workshop, November 8, 2017
    - The Impact and Importance of Digital Marketing Workshop, November 8, 2017
    - Using LinkedIn to Increase your Marketing and Sales Effort, November 14, 2017
    - Fiscal Year End Workshop, November 16, 2017
    - How to do Buisness with Dollar Bank, November 30, 2017
    - Trends Workshop, January 23, 2018
    - Implications of Tax Reform on Individual and Small Business Workshop, February 22, 2018
    - How to do Business with City of Pittsburgh, March 20, 2018
    - How to do Business with Duquesne Light Company, March 20, 2018
    - How to do Business with Pittsburgh Water and Sewer Authority, April 10, 2018
    - How to do Business with PJ Dick and Trumbull Corporation, April 24, 2018